Finding Aid for Michigan Memorial Phoenix Project Records, 1947-2003
Bentley Historical Library
- Research, 1948-2003
  - Research Grants, Nos. 1-816, 1948-1996
    - #401-#600
      - Qualification of the FNR as an Irradiation Damage Facility, G.S. Was, [600.] (Box 47)
    - #601-#800
      - Nuclear Proliferation and its Consequences for International Stability, J.D. Singer, [601.] (Box 47)
      - Isolation and Characterization of Cytochrome Oxidase Genes, L.I. Grossman, [602.] (Box 47)
      - Schistosome Membrane Antigen Modification by 60 Cobalt, G. Higashi, [603.] (Box 47)
      - I-123 Fatty Acid Scintigraphy, B. Shapiro, [604.] (Box 47)
      - Identification of the Human and Avian Erythrocyte D-glucose Transporters, C. Carter-Su, [605.] (Box 47)
      - Activation of Sertoli Cell Adenylate Cyclase by Germ Cells In Vitro, M.J. Welsh, [606.] (Box 47)
      - Experiments on Stress Corrosion Cracking of Zircaloy Fuel Cladding by an Expanding Mandrel Technique, J.S. King, [607.] (Box 47)
      - Radiocarbon Dating of Indian Cave Temples, W. Spink, [608.] (Box 47)
      - PCP Brain Distribution and Effects on Deoxyglucose Uptake, E. Domino, [609.] (Box 47)
      - Calmodulin-sensitive Adenylate Cyclase: Characterization and Alterations in Drug-induced Parkinsonism, M. Gnegy, [610.] (Box 47)
      - Mitochondrial Proteins in a Respiration-Defective Mutant, C. Whitfield, [611.] (Box 47)
      - Monoclonal Anti-idiotypic Antibodies and Self MHC Receptors, B. Wilson, [612.] (Box 47)
      - Scattering from Polyelectrolyte Solutions, A.Z. Akcasu, [613.] (Box 47)
      - A Seismological Study of the Lowermost Mantle Using Underground Nuclear Explosions, L.J. Ruff, [614.] (Box 47)
      - Thermophysics of Uranium/Thorium Substances of Nuclear Energy Import, E. Westrum, [615.] (Box 47)
      - Late Prehistoric Paleoenvironments and Cultural Adaptation in South-Eastern New Mexico, J.D. Speth, [616.] (Box 47)
      - An In vitro Study of Measles Virus Persistence, L.E. Fisher, [617.] (Box 47)
      - The Molecular Mechanism of Soluble Chloroplast Coupling Factor One, W. Frasch, [618.] (Box 47)
      - Chromosomal Integration & Excision of Salmonella Virulence Plasmids, G.W. Jones, [619.] (Box 47)
      - Glomerular Immune Complex Displacement by Charge Competition, R.C. Wiggins, [620.] (Box 47)
      - Irridium Anomalies at the Cretaceous -- Tertiary Boundary in Wyoming, E.J. Essene, [621.] (Box 47)
      - The Brittle-Ductile Transition, Is This the Detachment Zone for Crystalline Nappes?, D.V. Wiltschko, [622.] (Box 47)
      - Collisions of Ultra-high Energy Electrons with Thermal Atoms, J.C. Zorn, [623.] (Box 47)
      - Properties of the Growth Hormone Receptor, J. Schwartz, [624.] (Box 47)
      - In Vivo Assessment of Cholinergic Neutrotrnasmission, B.W. Agranoff, [625.] (Box 47)
      - DNA Relication and Mutagenesis, E.E. Dekker, [626.] (Box 47)
      - Labeled Essential Fatty Acid Conversions in Thyroid Induced Anuran Metamorphosis, F.L. Hoch, [627.] (Box 47)
      - Characterization of Human Specific T Cell Products, B. Richardson, [628.] (Box 47)
      - Preliminary Investigation Into Acoustic Emission Monitoring of Structural Integrity, E. Kannatey-Asibu, [629.] (Box 47)
      - Technical Requirements for Low Level Radioactive Waste Sites, J.E. Martin, [630.] (Box 47)
      - High Pressure Investigation of the Transport Properties of Graphite and Intercalation Compounds, C. Uher, [631.] (Box 47)
      - Effect of 2, 3-dihydroxybenzoic Acid on Phagocyte-Induces Lung Injury, L. Boxer, [632.] (Box 47)
      - Arachidonic Acid Stimulation of the Human Neutrophil Respiratory Burst, J.T. Curnutte, [633.] (Box 47)
      - TRNA Gene Expression, D. Engelke, [634.] (Box 47)
      - Regulation of Rat Pituitary Hyperplasia and Neoplasia, R. Lloyd, [635.] (Box 47)
      - Study of Chemotaxis Receptor Structure and Function, R. Nairn, [636.] (Box 47)
      - P-Bromospiroperidol: A Pituitary Imaging Agent, C. Otto (Box 47)
      - Solid-State Polymerization, C.G. Overberger, [638.] (Box 47)
      - Theories of Arms Races and Nuclear Confrontation, R. Axelrod, [639.] (Box 47)
      - Correction of Thalassemia in Mice by Gene Therapy, R.D. Erickson, [640.] (Box 47)
      - Nutrition and Sexual Maturation in Male Ground Squirrels, W. Holmes, [641.] (Box 47)
      - Comparison of Regional Cerebral Blood Flow with 123I-HIPDM/O15 --H2O, J. Juni, [642.] (Box 48)
      - Arachidonic Acid Metabolism by Human Alveolar Macrophage, J. Lynch, [643.] (Box 48)
      - Optimal Laser Plasma Heating, Z. Akcasu, [644.] (Box 48)
      - K, U and Th Abundances in the Earth's Upper Mantle, R.J. Arculus, [645.] (Box 48)
      - An Artificial Intelligence Approach to Nuclear Power Plant Diagnostics and Control Guidance, J.C. Lee, [646.] (Box 48)
      - Mitochondrial Metabolism of 2-Aminofluroene, M. Brabec, [647.] (Box 48)
      - Assessment of LH beta Sub-unit mRNA Amounts in Pituitaries of Sheep During Various Times of the Estrous Cycle, T. Landefeld, [648.] (Box 48)
      - Mechanisms of Neuronal Damage in a Model of Perinatal Brain Injury, F. Silverstein, [649.] (Box 48)
      - Spectroscopic Studies of Long Pulse Relativistic Electron Beam Produced Plasmas, M.L. Brake, [650.] (Box 48)
      - A Seismological Study of an Upper Mantle Velocity, T. Lay, [651.] (Box 48)
      - Magnetic Monopole Search at Gran Sasso, G. Tarle, [652.] (Box 48)
      - Investigations of Artificial Metallic Superlattices, C. Uher, [653.] (Box 48)
      - Molecular Genetics of Bioluminescence in fish, W. Brown, [654.] (Box 48)
      - Unique Surface Structures on Rheumatoid Synovial T Cells, D.A. Fox, [655.] (Box 48)
      - Explanation Model of Glioma Antigen Instability, P.E. McKeever, [656.] (Box 48)
      - Monoclonal Antibody Radioimmunodiagnosis of Transplant Rejection, R.L. Wahl, [657.] (Box 48)
      - Irradiation Enhanced Coal Liquefaction, D.E. Briggs, [658.] (Box 48)
      - Microautoradiography for Biodegradation Studies, R.B. Kapuscinski, [659.] (Box 48)
      - Measurement of the Diffusion of Boron in Silicon by Neutron Depth Profiling, D.H. Vincent, [660.] (Box 48)
      - Neutron Activation Analysis of Thirteenth Century Byzantine Silver Coins, R.P. Lindner, [661.] (Box 48)
      - Dopamine Receptor Binding and Regulation in Bovine and Goldfish Retina, M. Gnegy, [662.] (Box 48)
      - Molecular Biological Studies of Virulence Determining Factors of Moraxella Bovis, C.F. Marrs, [663.] (Box 48)
      - Sequencing of Genes Controlling Cellular Morphogenesis in Yeast, J. Pringle, [664.] (Box 48)
      - Isolation and Characterization of T-Cell Activation Genes, D. Shapiro, [665.] (Box 48)
      - Interactions Among Sorbates on Natural Sorbents, R.L. Curl, [666.] (Box 48)
      - Single Crystal Neutron Diffractometry, J.S. King, [667.] (Box 48)
      - Catalyst Characterization by Mossbauer Spectroscopy, J. Schwank, [668.] (Box 48)
      - Neutron Radiography to Detect Transport in Porous Media by Fingering, S. Wright, [669.] (Box 48)
      - Interaction of Growth Hormone and Gonadal Steroids in 3T3 Adipocytes, C. Foster, [670.] (Box 48)
      - Genetic Regulation of Mitochondrial Membrane Biogenesis, M. Greenberg, [671.] (Box 48)
      - Tissue-Specific Regulation of Amylase Genes, M. Meisler, [672.] (Box 48)
      - Genetics of Radiation Repair and Meiosis in Coprinus Cinereus, M. Zolan, [673.] (Box 48)
      - Search for Stellar Sources of High Energy Gamma Rays, C. Akerlof, [674.] (Box 48)
      - Intelligent Control Systems for Nuclear Reactors, D.K. Wehe, [675.] (Box 48)
      - Structure and Function of Thrombospondin, V. Dixit, [676.] (Box 48)
      - Expression of Measles Virus Matrix Protein Gene, L. Fisher, [677.] (Box 48)
      - Synthesis and Localization of Radioiodinated Bystemine Analogs, C. Otto, [678.] (Box 48)
      - Biochemical Gerontology of Neurotoxic Esterase, R. Richard, [679.] (Box 48)
      - 3-Phosphoglycerate-Dependent Protein Phosphorylation In Pancreatic Islets, T. Ueda, [680.] (Box 48)
      - Isotopic Ages and Signatures for Strategic Mineralization, A.N. Halliday, [681.] (Box 48)
      - Nuclear Moisture Density Probe for Geotechnical Research, R.D. Hryciw, [682.] (Box 48)
      - Acceleration Methods for Transport Problems, E. Larsen, [683.] (Box 48)
      - Studies on the Structure of the Rieske [2Fe-2S] Center, D.P. Ballou, [684.] (Box 48)
      - Mechanism of Transformation by c-sis, M. Clarke, [685.] (Box 48)
      - Radiobiological Approaches to Outer Segment Disassembly, D. Defoe, [686.] (Box 48)
      - Molecular Systematics of False Truffles, R. Fogel, [687.] (Box 48)
      - Granulomatous Inflammation and Interleukin-2, D. Remick, [688.] (Box 48)
      - Oxidan-Induced Arachidonic Acid Metabolism in the Alveolar Macrophage, P. Sporn, [689.] (Box 48)
      - Cis-Acting and Trans-Acting Gene-Regulatory Sequences, S. Tsubota, [690.] (Box 48)
      - Biochemical Basis of Platelet Dysfunction in Diabetes, A. Vinik, [691.] (Box 49)
      - A Microwave Pumped Excimer Laser, M.L. Brake, [692.] (Box 49)
      - Free Electron Maser Microwave Generators, R.H. Gilgenbach, [693.] (Box 49)
      - DNA Deletion/Splicing in Developing Tetrahymena Macronuclei, S.L. Allen, [694.] (Box 49)
      - Epigenetic Control of Muscle Differentiation and Regeneration, K.F. Barald, [695.] (Box 49)
      - Alveolar Epithelial Cell Arachidonic Acid Metabolism, J. Chauncey, [696.] (Box 49)
      - Development of Dysprosium Ferric Hydroxide Macroaggregates for Radiation Synorectomy: Initial Studies, R. Ike, [697.] (Box 49)
      - A Neutron Scattering Study of Metastable Phase Formation in the Solid State, M. Atzmon, [698.] (Box 49)
      - Trapped Monopole Search, M. Longo, [699.] (Box 49)
      - Dislocation-Hydrogen Correlation in Metals, G.C. Summerfield, [700.] (Box 49)
      - Rational Peptide Component Vaccines for Aids, K. Cease, [701.] (Box 49)
      - Interactions of GI Peptides with Normal or Regenerating Rat Liver, S. Raper, [702.] (Box 49)
      - Molecular Cloning of Soluble Suppressor Factor, S. Schwartz, [703.] (Box 49)
      - Trace Transition Metal Analysis in Semiconducting Materials, A. Francis, [704.] (Box 49)
      - Phylogenetic Analysis of Mollusca: Polyplacophora as Determined from Mitochondrial DNA Analysis, D. Eernisse, [705.] (Box 49)
      - Molecular Analysis of a T Cell Activating Protein, D.A. Fox, [706.] (Box 49)
      - Cellular Heterogeneity of Urokinase in Human Lung Disease, M. Gyetko, [707.] (Box 49)
      - Expression and Regulation of erbA mRNAs in Various Rat Organs, R. Koenig, [708.] (Box 49)
      - Halogenated Pyrimidine Induced Radiosensitization, T. Lawrence, [709.] (Box 49)
      - Labeling of the Glucocorticoid Receptor with Molybdenum-99, W. Pratt, [710.] (Box 49)
      - Mechanisms of Astrocyte Growth Inhibition by Heparin, P. Robertson, [711.] (Box 49)
      - Phospholipid Derivatives: A Possible Means for Delivering Drugs, V.C. Yang, [712.] (Box 49)
      - A Liquid Nitrogen Cerenkov Counter for the SMILI Light Isotope Spectrometer, G. Tarle, [713.] (Box 49)
      - The Social Context and Impact of Nuclear Energy in Brazil, C. Kottak, [714.] (Box 49)
      - Repopulation of Murine Hematopoietic Stem Cells with Mod..., R. Erickson, [715.] (Box 49)
      - Transcriptional Regulation of the Corticoropin-Releasing Hormone Gene, A. Seasholtz, [716.] (Box 49)
      - Expression of Synthetic Influenza Virus Genome Segments, M. Shaw, [717.] (Box 49)
      - Biological and Physio-Chemical Mechanisms of Sulfate Retention Along an Atmospheric Pollution Gradient, J.A. Witter, [718.] (Box 49)
      - Microscopic Imaging of Porous Media Using Neutron Radiography, H.S. Fogler, [719.] (Box 49)
      - A Fusion Approach to Advanced Propulsion, T. Kammash, [720.] (Box 49)
      - Model Catalytic Surfaces Prepared Using Ion Beam Techniques, L. Thompson, [721.] (Box 49)
      - Tectonic Setting of the Weeksboro-Lunksoos Lake Terraine, Maine Appalachians, B. van der Pluijm, [722.] (Box 49)
      - Biodegradation of Halogenated Solvents: Pathway for the Transformation of Vinyl Chloride, T. Vogel, [723.] (Box 49)
      - Morphological Correlates of Recovery of Function After Brain Tissue Transplantation, J. Becker, [724.] (Box 49)
      - Panhypoituitarism in Mice, S. Camper, [725.] (Box 49)
      - Molecular Identification of the Sigma Receptor: A Molecule with a Putative Role in Schizophrenia, B. Largent, [726.] (Box 49)
      - Active Regulation of Nuclear Localization, R. Lyons, [727.] (Box 49)
      - Regulation of Pulmonary Immune Responses by Alveolar Epithelial Cells, R. Paine, [728.] (Box 49)
      - Role of a Novel Neutrophil Chemotaxin in Lung Injury, R. Strieter, [729.] (Box 49)
      - Biosynthesis of UDP-N-Acetyl Muramic Acid, R. Woodard, [730.] (Box 49)
      - Trace Element and Oxygen Isotope Partitioning between CaCO3 and Water, J. O'Neil, [731.] (Box 49)
      - Defect Studies in Synthetic Diamond, S. Rand, [732.] (Box 49)
      - Hydrogen-Dislocation Correlation in Deformed Palladium, G. Summerfield, [733.] (Box 49)
      - Stopping and Trapping Neutral Molecules, J. Zorn, [734.] (Box 49)
      - Recurring Urinary Tract Infection: Risk Factors, B. Foxman, [735.] (Box 49)
      - Proto-Oncogene c-raf: in src Transformation, R. Jove, [736.] (Box 49)
      - Quantitation of ADP-Ribosylation of G-Proteins, G. Omann, [737.] (Box 49)
      - Role of Cytokines in Sepsis and Trauma, D. Remick, [738.] (Box 49)
      - Molecular Genetic Control of Localized Cell Expansion, J. Schiefelbein, [739.] (Box 49)
      - Pathogenesis of Perinatal HIV Infection, S. Schwartz, [740.] (Box 49)
      - The Effect of Radiation Transport on Heat Transfer Calculations in Reactor Safety, J. Holloway, [741.] (Box 49)
      - Arc Terrane Amalgamation and the Growth of Continents: An Isotopic Perspective, S. Mukasa, [742.] (Box 49)
      - A New Trigger for a Direct Photon Experiment, G. Snow, [743.] (Box 49)
      - Computations of Multi-Phase Flows, G. Tryggvason, [744.] (Box 49)
      - Molecular Genetic Control of Nerve Cell Determination in the Fruit Fly, R. Bodmer, [745.] (Box 50)
      - Complement Processing on Endothelium and Leukocyte Adhesion, R. Marks, [746.] (Box 50)
      - Characterization of Vitamin D3 Receptor Binding to DNA Promoter Elements, M.B. Parsons, [747.] (Box 50)
      - Are Ferns Ancient Polyploids (Do Ferns Contain Multiple Copies of Each Gene)?, E. Pichersky, [748.] (Box 50)
      - The Bar Gene In Drosophila Melanogaster, S. Tsubota, [749.] (Box 50)
      - Study of the Effects of Radnomness and Disorder on Phase Transitions, S. Dierker, [750.] (Box 50)
      - Characterization of Vitamin D3 Receptor Binding to DNA Promoter Elements, D. Martin, [751.] (Box 50)
      - Trace Element Signatures of Copper Mineralization Episodes at White Pine, Michigan, P. Meyers, [752.] (Box 50)
      - Soviet Nuclear Physicists as Arms-Control Advocates, M. Evangelista, [753.] (Box 50)
      - Neutron Activation Analysis of Ancient Roman Glass, E.L. Higashi, [754.] (Box 50)
      - Isolation of Human Renal Endothelial Cells and Characterization of Their Cytokine Regulatory Circuits, C. Blifeld, [755.] (Box 50)
      - Characterization of Regulatory Genes in Bacterial Pathogens, V. DiRita, [756.] (Box 50)
      - Radioimmunoassay for Growth-Hormone Binding Protein, C. Foster, [757.] (Box 50)
      - A Novel Strategy for Determining the Clonal Origin of Cells from Prepared Histologic Sections, T. Frank, [758.] (Box 50)
      - Signal Transduction by G-Proteins in the Retinal Pigment Epithelium, D. Thompson, [759.] (Box 50)
      - Pet Imaging of Implanted Radiotherapy Heavy Ion Beams to Monitor & Optimize Dose Delivery at Tumor Sites, F. Becchetti, [760.] (Box 50)
      - Investigation of the Interactions of Trace Elements & Ambient Acids in the Atmosphere, G. Keeler, [761.] (Box 50)
      - Polymer Bound Tetracyanobiimidazole as a Metal Ion Scavenger, P. Rasmussen, [762.] (Box 50)
      - Prototype Air-Cerenkov Surface Array for the Macro Detector, G. Tarle, [763.] (Box 50)
      - Development of a Cell Free Assay To Study Exocytosis, J. Francis, [764.] (Box 50)
      - Premature Transcriptional Arrest Mediated By Differential Binding of Nuclear Factors to DNA, J. Innis, [765.] (Box 50)
      - Embryonic Pigment Cell Lineages of the Sea Urchin, D. Livant, [766.] (Box 50)
      - Localization of Cytochrome c Oxidase mRNA in Heart, M. Lomax, [767.] (Box 50)
      - Physiological Relevance of FSH Heterogeneity, V. Padmanabhan, [768.] (Box 50)
      - Regulation of Lung Chemotactic Cytokine Networks By Specific Lymphokines, T. Standiford, [769.] (Box 50)
      - Linkage and Mapping of Breast Cancer to Chromosome 17, B. Weber, [770.] (Box 50)
      - Genetic Polymorphisms, Variation, and Divergence in Azolla Lam, W.J. Zimmerman, [771.] (Box 50)
      - Molecular Dynamics Study of Radiation Damage in Diamond, S. Fahy, [772.] (Box 50)
      - Calibration of the Timing of Global Climatic Change Using Automated Laser 40AR/30AR Dating, C. Hall, [773.] (Box 50)
      - Thermal Conductivity of Radiation-Damaged Diamond Films, C. Uher, [774.] (Box 50)
      - The Design of a Patient Locating, Positioning and Stabilizing Fixture for use in Radiation Therapy, A. Samuels, [775.] (Box 50)
      - Mechanism of Neutrophil Priming Growth Factor, K. Balazovich, [776.] (Box 50)
      - Identification of a RARE in the Thrombospond in Promoter, V. Castle, [777.] (Box 50)
      - Mutation Scanning in Alzheimer's Disease, J. Fink, [778.] (Box 50)
      - Identification of a Cellular Receptor for Measles Virus in Vero Cells, L. Fisher, [779.] (Box 50)
      - Cell Surface Receptor(s) for HSV, A.O. Fuller, [780.] (Box 50)
      - In Vivo DNA-Protein Interactions in Globin Gene Expression, D. Gumucio, [781.] (Box 50)
      - Function of the CD7 Antigen on Human T Cells, Y. Shimizu, [782.] (Box 50)
      - Evolution of the Male Sex-Determining Locus, Sry, in Mice, P. Tucker, [783.] (Box 50)
      - Variational Homogenization of Nuclear Reactor Cores, J. Holloway, [784.] (Box 50)
      - Development of Evaluative Techniques for Interactive Museum Exhibits based on Subnuclear Physics, G. Snow, [785.] (Box 50)
      - High-Precision Trace-Element Characterization of the Huitzila Obsidian Source, Sacatecas, Mexico, J. Parsons, [786.] (Box 50)
      - Localization of PLD Sensitive Phosphatidylcholine, R.A. Blackwood, [787.] (Box 50)
      - Cytokines in the Pathogenesis of Radiation Induced Lung Injury, J. Brieland, [788.] (Box 50)
      - Mechanisms of Upregulation of 5-Lipoxygenase in Alveolar Macrophages, M. Coffey, [789.] (Box 50)
      - Design of a Technetium Radiopharmaceutical for Detection of Cholinergic Neurons, R. Del Rosario, [790.] (Box 50)
      - Expression and Function of a Novel TNF-Induced Secreted Protein in Embryonic Development, L. Holzman, [791.] (Box 50)
      - The Role of Macrophage Inflammatory Protein-1 (MIP-1) in Pulmonary Cryptococcus Neoformans Infections, G. Huffnagle, [792.] (Box 50)
      - Gene Therapy of Leukocyte Adhesion Deficiency, J. Krauss, [793.] (Box 50)
      - Fullerene-Based Thin Film Neutron Radiation Detector, M. Bretz, [794.] (Box 50)
      - The Oxygen Fugacity of Hydrous Veins in the Earth's Mantel, R. Lange, [795.] (Box 50)
      - Regulation of Endomitotic DNA Synthesis in Human Erythroleukemia Cells, N.S. Datta, [796.] (Box 50)
      - Novel Neurogenic genes from embryonic stem cells, K.S. O'Shea, [797.] (Box 50)
      - Function of Brain/Gut Peptides in the Mouse, L. Samuelson, [798.] (Box 50)
      - Neutron Scattering Studies of Uranium Based Heavy Fermion Compounds, M. Aronson, [799.] (Box 50)
      - Neutron Activation Analysis of Reactor Soot for Rare-Earth/Fullerene Endohedral Complexes, A.H. Francis, [800.] (Box 50)
    - #801-865
      - Effect of Specific Bacteriophage T4 and Host Proteins on Accessibility of the Ribosome Binding Region of Phage rndB mRNA, G.R. Greenberg, [801.] (Box 51)
      - Missing, [802.] (Box 51)
      - Facility for Neutron Activation Analysis of Silver Coins, A. Gordus, [803.] (Box 51)
      - Regulation of Lung Epithelial Cell GMCSF, P. Christensen, [804.] (Box 51)
      - Proto-Oncogene Regulation and Action in Granulosa Cells: Growth Factor and Gondadotropin Interaction on AP-I Mediated Gene Transcription, G. Christman, [805.] (Box 51)
      - Cloning Genes Critical for Mammalian Limb Development, J. Innis, [806.] (Box 51)
      - Molecular Analysis of Drosophila Myosuppressin, R. Nichols, [807.] (Box 51)
      - Molecular Mechanisms of Peroxisome Biogenesis in Higher Plants, L. Olsen, [808.] (Box 51)
      - Development of an Advanced Hall Thruster for Use with Nuclear Powered Outer Planetary Space Probes, A. Gallimore, [809.] (Box 51)
      - Carborane-Vapor Plasmas for Disposition of Boronized Carbon Films, W. Getty, [810.] (Box 51)
      - Beta-Radiographs of Watermarks in 76 Early Manuscripts Containing Poems by John Doone, T.L. Pebworth, [811.] (Box 51)
      - Characterization of Heterophilic Binding Protein of the Homophilic Cell Adhesion Molecule Neuroglian, M. Hortsch, [812.] (Box 51)
      - The Role of IL-4 in Asthmatic Inflammation, N. Lukacs, [813.] (Box 51)
      - Biomonitoring of Toxic Metal Pollution in the Great Lakes Using Zebra Mussels, J. Nriagu, [814.] (Box 51)
      - Investigations of Optically Pumped 134Cs for Studies of Time Reversal Invariance in Beta-Decay, K. Coulter, [815.] (Box 51)
      - Advanced Material for Safe Nuclear Waste Repository, V. Li, [816.] (Box 51)
      - Effect of Specific Bacteriophage T4 and Host Proteins on Accessibility of the Ribosome Binding Region of Phage rndB mRNA, G.R. Greenberg, [801] (Box 51)
      - Missing, [802] (Box 51)
      - Facility for Neutron Activation Analysis of Silver Coins, A. Gordus, [803] (Box 51)
      - Regulation of Lung Epithelial Cell GMCSF, P. Christensen, [804] (Box 51)
      - Proto-Oncogene Regulation and Actionin Granulosa Cells: Growth Factor and Gondadotropin Interaction on AP-I Mediated Gene Transcription, G. Christman, [805] (Box 51)
      - Cloning Genes Critical for Mammalian Limb Development, J. Innis, [806] (Box 51)
      - Molecular Analysis of Drosophila Myosuppressin, R. Nichols, [807] (Box 51)
      - Molecular Mechanisms of Peroxisome Biogenesis in Higher Plants, L. Olsen, [808] (Box 51)
      - Development of an Advanced Hall Thruster for Use with Nuclear Powered Outer Planetary Space Probes, A. Gallimore, [809] (Box 51)
      - Carborane-Vapor Plasmas for Disposition of Boronized Carbon Films, W. Getty, [810] (Box 51)
      - Beta-Radiographs of Watermarks in 76 Early Manuscripts Containing Poems by John Doone, T.L. Pebworth, [811] (Box 51)
      - Characterization of Heterophilic Binding Protein of the Homophilic Cell Adhesion Molecule Neuroglian, M. Hortsch, [812] (Box 51)
      - The Role of IL-4 in Asthmatic Inflammation, N. Lukacs, [813] (Box 51)
      - Biomonitoring of Toxic Metal Pollution in the Great Lakes Using Zebra Mussels, J. Nriagu, [814] (Box 51)
      - Investigations of Optically Pumped 134Cs for Studies of Time Reversal Invariance in Beta-Decay, K. Coulter, [815] (Box 51)
      - Advanced Material for Safe Nuclear Waste Repository, V. Li, [816] (Box 51)
      - Analysis of a Novel Class of Genes Controlling Flower Development, S. Clark, [817] (Box 53)
      - Rapid Identification of Quantitative Loci in Drosophila, G. Gibson, [818] (Box 53)
      - Design of an Ultra-Low Background Gamma Spectroscopy System, D. Hamby, [819] (Box 53)
      - Neurotransmitter Storage: In Situ Mapping of Vesicular Glutamate Uptake, P. Kist, [820] (Box 53)
      - The Regulation of Cell Polarity in Caulobacter, J. Maddock, [821] (Box 53)
      - Adaptive Directional Meshes for Computation Particle Transport, J. Holloway, [822] (Box 53)